<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hath_Wasi</string>
    <string name="text01">•Hath Wasi is a traditional Sri Lankan card game which is played by ONLY 3 PLAYERS.</string>
    <string name="text02">•This game is played only using cards greater than 5 of all suits (Order of play – A>K>Q>10>9>8>7>6). Therefore, the selected 36 cards will be dealt among the three players EQUALLY (12 each) and dealing of cards will happen anticlockwise.</string>
    <string name="text03">•In the FIRST ROUND the HUMAN PLAYER will get a chance to BID the trump for the game, which means the human player should check for 7 possible chances to win the game. If 7 possible chances cannot be found, the player will have the OPTION TO PASS the bidding chance to the next player (This happens anticlockwise).</string>
    <string name="text04">•In case, if all the players pass the chance, the round will be cancelled and the shuffling and dealing of cards will happen continuously until a player bid.</string>
    <string name="text05">•The PLAYER WHO BIDS will be the INDIVIDUAL TEAM and the OTHER 2 PLAYERS will be the OPPOSITION TEAM.</string>
    <string name="text06">•The player who bids will start the game by playing the first card and the playing of cards will happen in the anticlockwise direction.</string>
    <string name="text07">•The team which played the card with the HIGHEST value will receive 2 POINTS and if its the team with 2 PLAYERS, EACH player will receive 1 POINT.</string>
    <string name="text08">•The first team to WIN 7 CHANCES will WIN the game and once a team wins (7 chances), the game will NO LONGER be CONTINUED even if there are more cards left in hand.</string>
    <string name="text09">•The score of each player will be updated in the SCORE BOARD at the end of each game which can be viewed under the Score Board option in the Main page.</string>
    <string name="text10">•Instructions on how to play the game Hath Wasi and other special features available in the application are mentioned in the INSTRUCTIONS page on the Main page.</string>
    <string name="text11">Special Features</string>
    <string name="text12">•The trump which was selected at bidding for the round will be indicated in the middle of the score bar throughout the game.</string>
    <string name="text13">•All 12 cards dealt for the human player will be organized according to the category and in ascending order of each category.</string>
    <string name="text14">•The scores of each team will be updated at the end of each round of play accordingly on the score bar throughout the game.</string>
</resources>
